Register to The Ernest Trow Carter Papers
Yale University Music Library
- Music by Carter, 1879-1968; Series I; 13.75' (33 boxes)
  - Songs, I.E
    - [Baltimore, our Baltimore] Baltimore, Our Baltimore / music by "Spero"; words by Folger McKinsey. -- ca. 1915 Dec. 1., 1 manuscript score ([4] p.); 35 cm. (Box 27, Folder 246)
    - [Baltimore, our Baltimore] Baltimore, Our Baltimore: song for medium voice with piano accompaniment / Music by "Spero"; Words by Folger McKinsey. -- [ca. 1915 Dec. 1]., 1 manuscript score (5 p.); 33 cm. (Box 27, Folder 246)
      Note from Carter to contest judges laid in
    - [Baltimore, our Baltimore. Text] Baltimore, Our Baltimore / [words by] Folger McKinsey., [1] leaf; 24 cm. (Box 27, Folder 246)
      With: rules for Municipal Song Contest of the City of Baltimore
      Note: competition closed 1915 Dec. 1
    - [Buy low, Abie] Buy low, Abie: Lullaby / Words and Music by Ernest Carter., 1 manuscript score ([3] p.); 35 cm. (Box 27, Folder 247)
    - [Buy low, Abie] Buy low, Abie: Lullaby / Ernest Carter., 1 manuscript score ([3] p.); 34 cm. (Box 27, Folder 247)
    - [Buy low, Abie. Text] Buy Low, Abie: Lullaby., [1] sheet; 28 cm. (Box 27, Folder 247)
    - [Cheerful road. Text] The Cheerful Road: (A Ballad) / Louis E. Weekman., [1] sheet; 28 cm. (Box 27, Folder 248)
      Words to a song?
    - [Christmas carol] Christmas Carol / [music by] Ernest Carter; [words by] P. Gerhardt; trans. Winkworth. -- 1901 Nov. 11-12., 1 manuscript score ([2] p.); 34 cm. (Box 27, Folder 248)
    - [Columbia, Cosmopolis] Columbia, Cosmopolis / Words + Music of verse by ""; Words + Music of Chorus by "Cosmop.", 1 manuscript score ([2] p.); 32 cm. (Box 27, Folder 249)
      For voice and piano
    - [Columbia, Cosmopolis] Columbia, Cosmopolis: Song for medium voice with piano accompaniment., 1 manuscript score ([2] p.); 34 cm. (Box 27, Folder 249)
    - [Columbia, Cosmopolis. Text] Columbia, Cosmopolis / Words + Music of Verse by ""; Words and Music of Chorus by "Cosmop.", [1] sheet; 28 cm. (Box 27, Folder 249)
      Typescript.
      Three copies, one with pencil markings
    - [Columbia, Cosmopolis. Text] Columbia, Cosmopolis / Words & Music of verse by ""; Words & Music of Chorus by "Cosmop.", [1] sheet; 28 cm. (Box 27, Folder 249)
    - [Deer in forest hiding. Text], [1] sheet; 28 cm. (Box 27, Folder 250)
    - [Does he love me?] Does he love me / Ernest Carter., 1 manuscript score ([3] p.); 31 cm. (Box 27, Folder 250)
    - [For glory] For Glory / Words and Music by Ernest Carter., 1 manuscript score ([3] p.); 34 cm. (Box 27, Folder 250)
    - [Fountain in the park] Fountain in the Park: (song for medium voice) / Music by Ernest Carter; words by Louis E. Weekman. -- 1922 Dec., 1 manuscript score (5 p.); 33 cm. (Box 27, Folder 251)
    - [Fountain in the park] The Fountain in the Park: song / Music by Ernest Carter; words by Louis E. Weekman, 1 manuscript score (5 p.); 35 cm. (Box 27, Folder 251)
    - [Fountain in the park. Text] Fountain in the park / Louis E. Weekman. -- ca. 1924 Nov. 11., [1] sheet; 28 cm. (Box 27, Folder 251)
      Four other typescript texts laid in
    - [French dolly] French Dolly / Ernest Carter. -- 1911 Apr. 2-3., 1 manuscript score (10 p.) + 12 parts; 28-35 cm. (Box 27, Folder 252)
      For voice and orchestra
      Dates from bottom left corner of parts
      Parts include fl., ob., hn., triangle, vln. I (2),vln.II (2), vla., vlc., d.b., voice (2, photocopies)
    - [French dolly] French dolly: song for mezzo-soprano with piano accompaniment / Ernest Carter., 1 manuscript score (5 p.); 34 cm. (Box 27, Folder 252)
    - [French dolly] French Dolly: or Doll Lullaby and Dance / Words and Music by Ernest Carter., 1 manuscript score (4 p.); 35 cm. (Box 27, Folder 252)
      On title page: old-uncorrected
    - [French dolly] French Dolly: or Doll Lullaby and Dance / words and music by Ernest Carter., 1 manuscript score ([3] p.); 34 cm. (Box 27, Folder 252)
      Holograph signed, in ink with pencil additions
    - [French dolly] French Dolly: song for mezzo soprano with piano-forte accompaniment / by Ernest Carter., 1 manuscript score ([5] p.); 34 cm. (Box 27, Folder 252)
    - [French dolly] Darling Dolly / words + music by Ernest Carter., 1 manuscript score ([4] p.); 34 cm. (Box 27, Folder 252)
      Holograph signed, in pencil and ink
    - [French dolly] French Dolly: song for mezzo-soprano with piano-forte accompaniment / by Ernest Carter., 1 manuscript score ([5] p.); 34 cm. (Box 27, Folder 252)
    - [French dolly] French Dolly: Dolly Lullaby and Dance / Words and Music by Ernest Carter. -- 1911., 1 manuscript score ([4] p.); 34 cm. (Box 27, Folder 252)
      Note on p. [1]: 1911 copy
    - [French dolly] French Dolly / words and music by Ernest Carter., 1 manuscript score (5 p.); 34 cm. (Box 27, Folder 252)
      On title page: Polly
    - [French dolly (Sketches)] Dance to French Dolly., [1] sheet of music; 35 cm. (Box 27, Folder 252)
    - [French dolly. Text] French dolly: or Doll lullaby / Words and Music by Ernest Carter., [2] sheets; 28 cm. (Box 27, Folder 252)
      Three copies with pencil markings laid in
    - [Gold and love for dearie] Gold and Love for Dearie: (a Cornish lullaby) / the poem by Eugene Field; the music by Ernest Carter. -- New York: William Maxwell Music Co., c1904., 1 score (7 p.); 35 cm. (Box 27, Folder 253)
      Pl. no.: 639-6
    - [Gold and love for dearie] Gold and love for Dearie: Cornish lullaby / [music by] Ernest Carter; [words by] Eugene Field., 1 manuscript score (6 p.); 34 cm. (Box 27, Folder 253)
    - [Gold and love for dearie] Gold and Love for Dearie: (Cornish lullaby) / [music by] Ernest Carter; [words by] Eugene Field., 1 manuscript score (4 p.); 34 cm. (Box 27, Folder 253)
    - [He must woo it, he must win it] He must woo it, he must win it / words by Frank L. Stanton; music by Ernest Carter., 1 manuscript score ([2] p.); 34 cm. (Box 27, Folder 254)
    - [Huntin' for a rose] Huntin' for a rose / Words by Frank L. Stanton; Music by Ernest Carter. -- c1903., 1 manuscript score ([2] p.); 34 cm. (Box 28, Folder 255)
      On title page: for high voice in F
    - [Huntin' for a rose] Huntin' for a rose / Words by Frank L. Stanton; Music by Ernest Carter. -- New York: Luckhardt & Belder, c1903., 1 score (3 p.); 36 cm. (Box 28, Folder 255)
      Pl. no.: L. & B. 1829-2
    - [Huntin' for a rose] When a feller goes a huntin for a rose: Song for Baritone or Mezzo-Soprano with piano forte accompaniment / [music by] Ernest Carter; Words by Frank L. Stanton., 1 manuscript score ([3] p.); 34 cm. (Box 28, Folder 255)
    - [Huntin' for a rose] Huntin' for a rose / Music by Ernest Carter; Words by Frank L. Stanton., 1 manuscript score ([2] p.); 34 cm. (Box 28, Folder 255)
    - [Huntin' for a rose] When a feller goes a huntin for a rose / [music by] Ernest Carter; Words by Frank L. Stanton., 1 manuscript score ([2] p.); 34 cm. (Box 28, Folder 255)
      Inscription on title page: To the Author of "Songs after work" with the Composer's compliments
    - [I made another garden] I made another garden: song for baritone, alto, mezzo soprano / Words by Robert O'Shaughnessy; Music by Ernest Trow Carter., 1 manuscript score ([5] p.); 34 cm. (Box 28, Folder 256)
      Note on title page: To Mr. Francis Fisher Powers, New York
      Sketch on title page verso; an addition laid in
    - [I made another garden] I made another garden: song for low voice with pianoforte accompaniment / Words by Robert O'Shaughnessy; Music by Ernest Carter., 1 manuscript score ([6] p.); 34 cm. (Box 28, Folder 256)
    - [I made another garden] I made another garden: song for low voice with pianoforte accompaniment / Words by Robert O'Shaughnessy; Music by Ernest Carter., 1 manuscript score (6 p.); 34 cm. (Box 28, Folder 256)
    - [I sing of a glorious land] I Sing of a Glorious Land: Song in Unison with Piano Accompaniment / Music by Spero., 1 manuscript score ([3] p.); 34 cm. (Box 28, Folder 257)
    - [I sing of a glorious land] I Sing of a Glorious Land: Song in Unison with Piano Accompaniment / Music by Spero i.e. Ernest Carter. -- ca. 1936 Jan. 8., 1 manuscript score ([2] p.); 33 cm. (Box 28, Folder 257)
      Holograph signed, in ink with pencil note
      Date appears next to stamp on title page: MANUSCRIPT REC'D
    - [I sing of a glorious land; arr.] I Sing of a Glorious Land: Song for Two Voices with Piano Accompaniment / Music by Spero. -- ca. 1936 Jan. 8., 1 manuscript score ([3] p.); 33 cm. (Box 28, Folder 257)
    - [I sing of a glorious land; arr.] I Sing of a Glorious Land: Song for Three Voices with Piano Accompaniment / Music by Spero. -- ca. 1936 Jan. 8., 1 manuscript score ([3] p.); 33 cm. (Box 28, Folder 257)
    - [I think of you] I Think of You: in C minor: Song for High Voice with Piano-forte accompaniment and Violin ad libitum / Music by Ernest Carter. -- ca. 1915 Jun. 5., 1 manuscript score (6 p.) + 2 parts; 35 cm. (Box 28, Folder 258)
      On title page: To my friend Martin Richardson with compliments Ernest Carter
      Date on bottom left corner of one part: 1915 Jun. 5
    - [I think of you] I Think of You: in C minor: Song for High Voice with Piano-forte accompaniment and Violin ad libitum / Music by Ernest Carter. -- ca. 1915 Jun. 5, 1 manuscript score (6 p.) + 1 part; 34 cm. (Box 28, Folder 258)
      Date on bottom left corner of part: 1915 Jun. 5
    - [I think of you] I Think of You: in A minor: Song for Medium Voice With Piano-forte accompaniment and Violin ad libitum / Music by Ernest Carter. -- 1915 May 17., 1 manuscript score (6 p.) + 1 part; 34 cm. (Box 28, Folder 258)
      Date on bottom left corner of title page: 1915 May 17
      Extra violin part laid in
    - [I think of you] I Think of You / Words by Madison Cawein; Music by Ernest Carter. -- c1904., 1 score ([6] p.) + 1 part; 35 cm. (Box 28, Folder 258)
      For soprano, piano, and violin obligato
      Three copies, with pencil and ink additions by Carter, one part missing
    - [I think of you] I Think of You / Words by Madison Cawein; Music by Ernest Carter. -- c1904., 1 score (6 p.) + 1 part; 34 cm. (Box 28, Folder 258)
      On title page: C minor copy
      Two copies, one with pencil and ink additions by Carter, and two extra parts laid in
    - [I think of you] I Think of You: in A minor: Song for Medium Voice With Piano-forte accompaniment and Violin ad libitum / Music by Ernest Carter. -- c1904., 1 manuscript score (6 p.) + 1 part; 34 cm. (Box 28, Folder 258)
      Date on bottom left corner of score and part: 1914 Apr. 11
    - [I think of you] I Think of You / [music by] Ernest Carter; Words by Madison Cawein., 1 manuscript score ([3] p.); 34 cm. (Box 28, Folder 258)
    - [I think of you] I Think of You / Words by Madison Cawein; Music by Ernest Carter., 1 manuscript score ([3] p.); 36 cm. (Box 28, Folder 258)
    - [I think of you] I Think of You / Words by Madison Cawein; Music by Ernest Carter., 1 manuscript score (6 p.); 34 cm. (Box 28, Folder 258)
      For voice, piano, and violin obligato
    - [I think of you] I Think of You: Song for Soprano or Tenor with accompaniment for piano forte (violin obligato ad libitum) / Words by Madison Cawein; Music by Ernest Carter. -- c1904., 1 manuscript score ([4] p.) + 1 part; 31-33 cm. (Box 28, Folder 258)
      Words by Cawein pasted to title page
    - [I think of you] I Think of You / Words by Madison Cawein; Music by Ernest Carter., 1 manuscript score (6 p.); 35 cm. (Box 28, Folder 258)
    - [I think of you] I Think of You: in A minor: For Baritone with Obligato for Violin and Piano-forte accompaniment / Music by Ernest Carter. -- c1904., 1 manuscript score ([5] p.) + 1 part; 35 cm. (Box 28, Folder 258)
      At end: OK 1907 Nov 14, 1913 Feb 20
      Note on part: Blue pencil suggestions by Maurice Milcke, fall of 1914
    - [I think of you] I Think of You / Words by Madison Cawein; Music by Ernest Carter. -- c1904., 1 manuscript score ([6] p.) + 1 part; 34 cm. (Box 28, Folder 258)
      For soprano, piano, and optional violin
      Date on title page and at end: 1907 Nov 14
    - [I think of you] I Think of You / Words by Madison Cawein; Music by Ernest Carter. -- c1904., 1 manuscript score ([6] p.) + 1 part (photocopy); 34 cm. (Box 28, Folder 258)
      Part contains an addition in Carter's hand pasted on
    - [I think of you] I Think of You: in A minor: For Baritone with Obligato for Horn in F and piano-forte accompaniment / Music by Ernest Carter. -- c1904., 1 manuscript score (5 p.) + 1 part; 34 cm. (Box 28, Folder 258)
    - [I think of you] I Think of You: in A minor: For Baritone with obligato for Horn in F and piano-forte accompaniment / Music by Ernest Carter. -- c1904., 1 manuscript score (5 p.); 34 cm. (Box 28, Folder 258)
    - [I think of you] I Think of You: in A minor: For Baritone with obligato for Horn in F and piano-forte accompaniment / Music by Ernest Carter., 1 manuscript score (5 p.); 35 cm. (Box 28, Folder 258)
    - [I think of you] I Think of You: in A minor: For Baritone with obligato for Horn in F and piano forte accompaniment / Music by Ernest Carter. -- c1904., 1 manuscript score (5 p.) + 1 part; 32-34 cm. (Box 28, Folder 258)
      Bottom left corner of title page and part dated 1911 Sep. 23
    - [I think of you] I Think of You. -- 1904-1934., 14 manuscript parts; 31-33cm. (Box 28, Folder 258)
      Holographs, in ink (in part, photocopies)
      Miscellaneous parts for violin, violoncello, and horn
    - [I think of you (Sketches)] 1 manuscript sheet of music; 32 cm., Holograph in pencil (Box 28, Folder 258)
    - [I'd like to take a trip to heaven] I'd Like to Take a Trip to Heaven / Music by Ernest Carter; Words by W.D. Neale., 1 manuscript score ([3] p.); 34 cm. (Box 28, Folder 259)
    - [I'd like to take a trip to heaven] I'd Like to Take a Trip to Heaven / Music by Hal Trowe; Words by W.D. Neale., 1 manuscript score ([3] p.); 33 cm. (Box 28, Folder 259)
      Holograph, in ink
      In parenthesis after Trowe: Ernest Carter
    - [I'd like to take a trip to heaven] I'd Like to Take a Trip to Heaven / Music by Hal Trowe; Words by W.D.Neale., 1 manuscript score ([3] p.); 33 cm. (Box 28, Folder 259)
    - [I'd like to take a trip to heaven. Text] A trip to heaven / Music by Hal Trow (Ernest Carter); Words by W.D. Neale., [1] sheet; 28 cm. (Box 28, Folder 259)
      Two copies, as well as another typescript text laid in
    - [Ich baute einen Garten noch für meine neue Lieb. Text], [1] sheet (3 p.); 22 cm. (Box 28, Folder 259)
      Uniform title from first line
    - [Jesus, tender shepherd] Jesus, Tender Shepherd, Hear Me / Music by Ernest Carter; Words by M. Duncan., 1 manuscript score ([2] p.); 34 cm. (Box 28, Folder 260)
    - [Jesus, tender shepherd] Jesus, Tender Shepherd / Music by Ernest Carter; Words by M. Duncan., 1 manuscript score ([2] p.); 34 cm. (Box 28, Folder 260)
    - [Jesus, tender shepherd] Jesus, Tender Shepherd / Music by Ernest Carter; Words by M. Duncan., 1 manuscript score ([2] p.); 34 cm. (Box 28, Folder 260)
    - [Kids at home] The Kids at Home: (Chopsticks): Song for Medium Voice / by Ernest Carter; Based on traditional Chopsticks tune., 1 manuscript score ([2] p.); 32 cm. (Box 28, Folder 261)
      Negative and positive photocopies laid in
    - [Kids at home] The Kids at Home: Song for medium voice / by Ernest Carter., 1 manuscript score ([2] p.); 32 cm. (Box 28, Folder 261)
    - [Kids at home. Text] The Kids At Home: (Chopsticks) / By Ernest Carter., [1] sheet; 22 cm. (Box 28, Folder 261)
    - [Mabel's coming home from college] Mabel's Coming Home from College: Baritone Solo / Music by Ernest Carter., 1 manuscript score ([1] sheet); 35 cm. (Box 28, Folder 262)
      For baritone and piano
    - [Maleezy boonah] Maleezy Boonah: Song / by Ernest Carter. -- ca. 1934 Sep. 4., 1 manuscript score ([2] p.); 26 cm. (Box 28, Folder 262)
      On title page: OK - Copied by Otto Fessler Sept. 4/34
    - [Mammy's growin' ole] Mammy's Growin' Ole / [music by] Ernest Carter; [words by] James D. Corrothers. -- 1900 Aug. 28., 1 manuscript score ([1] sheet); 31 cm. (Box 28, Folder 263)
    - [Mammy's growin' ole] Mammy's Growin' Ole: Negro Melody: for medium voice with piano accompaniment / Words by James D. Corrothers; Music by Ernest Carter., 1 manuscript score ([2] p.); 35 cm. (Box 28, Folder 263)
    - [Mammy's growin' ole] Mammy's Growin' Ole: Negro Melody: for medium voice with piano accompaniment / Words by James D. Corrothers; Music by Ernest Carter., 1 manuscript score ([2] p.); 34 cm. (Box 28, Folder 263)
      Sheet with printed text pasted on
    - [Mammy's growin' ole] Mammy's Growin' Ole: Song for medium voice with piano accompaniment / Words by James D. Corrothers; Music by Ernest Carter., 1 manuscript score (4 p.); 35 cm. (Box 28, Folder 263)
    - [Mammy's growin' ole] Mammy's Growin' Ole: Song for medium voice with piano accompaniment / Words by James D. Corrothers; Music by Ernest Carter., 1 manuscript score (4 p.); 34 cm. (Box 28, Folder 263)
    - [Mammy's growin' ole (Sketches)] 1922 Nov. 22., [1] sheet of music; 33 cm. (Box 28, Folder 263)
      Holograph, in pencil
    - [Mammy's growin' ole. Text] Mammy's Growin Ole., [1] sheet; 28 cm. (Box 28, Folder 263)
      Words by James D. Corrothers
    - [Mammy's growin' ole. Text] Mammy's Growin' Ole / James D. Corrothers., [1] sheet; 28 cm. (Box 28, Folder 263)
      Two copies, one with pencil markings, as well as another typescript text laid in
    - [Man behind the gun] The Man Behind the Gun: (Irish Song): with piano accompaniment / Words + music by Ernest Carter., 1 manuscript score ([3] p.); 34 cm. (Box 28, Folder 264)
    - [Man behind the gun. Text] The man behind the gun., [1] sheet; 27 cm. (Box 28, Folder 264)
      Three other typescript texts with pencil additions laid in, two entitled "Mr. Dooley's man behind the gun"
    - [Merry Christmas] A Merry Christmas: to a modern composer / by a modern composer. -- 1930 Dec. 25., [1] sheet of music; 12 x 26 cm. (Box 28, Folder 265)
      Note: sent to Ken Clark anonymously
    - [Merry Christmas] A Merry Christmas to a modern composer / by a modern composer. -- 1930 Dec. 25., 1 manuscript score ([1] sheet); 12 x 26 cm. (Box 28, Folder 265)
    - [Mountain bells yodel] Matterhorn Yodel / Musik von Ernest Carter. -- ca. 1896 Jun., 1 manuscript score ([7] p.); 34 cm. (Box 28, Folder 266)
      For soprano, tenor, and orchestra
      Words in English
      Note on title page: As sung in Wintergarten Berlin, June, 1896, by Dagmar + DeCelli
    - [Mountain bells yodel] Mountain Bells Yodel: Duet for Soprano Yodel and Tenor, oder Baryton with small orchestra., 1 manuscript score (6 p.) + 11 parts; 13-35 cm. (Box 28, Folder 266)
      Small vocal part with German words laid in
    - [Mountain bells yodels (Sketches)], [2] sheets of music; 12 x 26 cm., 15 x 25 cm. (Box 28, Folder 266)
      Holographs, in part signed, in ink
      Two sketches ?
    - [Mutterlied] Volkslied: Es stand ein grosses Zimmer Leer / Music by Ernest Carter., 1 manuscript score ([2] p.); 34 cm. (Box 28, Folder 267)
      On p. 1 "Volkslied" is crossed out and "Mutterlied - Im Volkston" is written above it
    - [Mutterlied] Volkslied: Es stand ein grosses Zimmer Leer / Ernest Carter., 1 manuscript score ([1] sheet); 34 cm. (Box 28, Folder 267)
    - [Mutterlied] Mutterlied - Im Volkston: Es stand ein grosses Zimmer Leer / Music by Ernest Carter., 1 manuscript score ([2] p.); 35 cm. (Box 28, Folder 267)
    - [My heart's a wa' up in the bonnie Hielands] [Music by] Ernest Carter. -- 1930 Aug. 27., 1 manuscript score ([1] sheet); 33 cm. (Box 28, Folder 268)
      Title from first line
    - [Oh, you mustn't mind a little thing like that (Sketches)] Oh, you mustn't a little thing like that: topical song / Words + Music by Ernest Trow Carter. -- 1893., 1 manuscript score ([1] sheet); 34 cm. (Box 28, Folder 269)
    - [Old Glory] Old Glory / Words by Thos Dunn English; Music by Ernest Carter., 1 manuscript score ([3] p.); 34 cm. (Box 28, Folder 270)
    - [Old Glory] Old Glory / [music by] Ernest Carter; Words by Thos. Dunn English., 1 manuscript score ([3] p.); 34 cm. (Box 28, Folder 270)
    - [Old Glory's waving with the flags] Chorus / Music by Ernest Carter; Words by Mabel Carter. -- 1918., 1 manuscript score ([1] sheet); 34 cm. (Box 28, Folder 271)
      Incomplete, chorus only
      Notes: Chorus (Mar 4/18); Words by Mabel Carter Summer 1918
    - [Old Glory's waving with the flags. Text] Words by Mabel Carter. -- 1918., [1] sheet; 17 cm. (Box 28, Folder 271)
    - [Old Martin Luther] Old Martin Luther / Words and Music by Ernest Carter., 1 manuscript score ([3] p.); 35 cm. (Box 28, Folder 272)
      Note on title page: Changed for "Blonde Donna"
    - [Past and the morrow] The Past and the Morrow / Music by Ernest Carter; Words by Geo. Force Parker., 1 manuscript score ([3] p.); 34 cm. (Box 28, Folder 273)
    - [Past and the morrow] The Past and The Morrow / Words by Geo. Force Parker; Music by Ernest Carter., 1 manuscript score ([4] p.); 34 cm. (Box 28, Folder 273)
    - [Past and the morrow] The Past and the Morrow / Words by Geo. Force Parker; Music by Ernest Carter., 1 manuscript score ([3] p.); 34 cm. (Box 28, Folder 273)
    - [Past and the morrow. Text] The Past and the Morrow / Force Parker., [1] sheet; 28 cm. (Box 28, Folder 273)
    - [Princeton's Old Guard's song (Sketches)] Princeton's Old Guards Song / Music by Ernest Carter. -- 1923 May 11., [1] manuscript sheet of music; 34 cm. (Box 28, Folder 274)
      Note: begun May 11/23
    - [Princeton's Old Guard's song. Text] Princeton's Old Guard's Song / Words by Joseph D. Baucus '86. -- ca. 1910., [1] sheet; 22 cm. (Box 28, Folder 274)
      Note: Respectfully dedicated to Princeton's Old Guard - June, 1910
      Contains correction in Carter's hand
    - [Remember the telephone girl] Remember the Telephone Girl / Words + Music by Ernest Carter., 1 manuscript score ([3] p.); 32 cm. (Box 28, Folder 275)
    - [Remember the telephone girl] Remember the Telephone Girl / Words and Music by Ernest Carter., 1 manuscript score (5 p.); 33 cm. (Box 28, Folder 275)
    - [Remember the telephone girl. Text] Remember the Telephone Girl / [words by] Ernest Carter. -- 1920 Sep. 17., [1] sheet; 28 cm. (Box 28, Folder 275)
    - [Remember the telephone girl. Text] Remember the telephone girl / Ernest Carter. -- 1920 Sep. 17., [1] sheet; 28 cm. (Box 28, Folder 275)
    - [Rosemary] Rosemary / [music by] Ernest Carter; [words by] Jane Dowling. -- 1904-1915., 1 manuscript score ([4] p.); 35 cm. (Box 28, Folder 276)
      On bottom of first p.: Copyright, 1904, by The William Maxwell Music Co. (in the key of C)
      On bottom left corner of first p.: May 13/15
      On title page: in F
    - [Rosemary] Rosemary / Words by Jane Dowling; Music by Ernest Carter., 1 manuscript score ([3] p.); 34 cm. (Box 28, Folder 276)
    - [Rosemary] Rosemary / Words by Jane Dowling; Music by Ernest Carter., 1 manuscript score ([3] p.); 34 cm. (Box 28, Folder 276)
    - [Rosemary] Rosemary / Words by Jane Dowling; Music by Ernest Carter., 1 manuscript score ([3] p.); 34 cm. (Box 28, Folder 276)
    - [Rosemary] Rosemary: Song / words by Jane Dowling / the music by Ernest Carter. -- New York: The William Maxwell Music Co., c1904., 1 score (6 p.); 35 cm. (Box 28, Folder 276)
      Pl.no.: 645-4
      Two copies, one marked
    - [Song of Tahawus] The Song of Tahawas: Song for medium voice with piano-forte accompaniment / Poem by Alfred L. Donalson [sic]; Music by Ernest Carter. -- ca. 1920 May 24., 1 manuscript score (6 p.); 34 cm. (Box 28, Folder 277)
      On title page: B minor
      On bottom left corner of title page: OK May 24/20
    - [Song of Tahawus] The Song of Tahawas: Song for medium voice with pianoforte accompaniment / Poem by Alfred L. Donaldson; Music by Ernest Carter., 1 manuscript score (6 p.); 34 cm. (Box 28, Folder 277)